{
	"name": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice",
	"cards": [
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-1",
			"front": "Which step in EMS decision making comes after a patient has been transferred?\n\nA. Team communication\nB. Planning\nC. Outcome evaluation\nD. Data gathering\nSee Critical Thinking and Clinical Decision Making in EMS",
			"back": "Outcome evaluation"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-2",
			"front": "In an interdependent group, when one person fails:\n\nA. that person is fired.\nB. pay is withheld.\nC. management will be changed.\nD. everyone fails.\nSee Dependent, Independent, and Interdependent Groups",
			"back": "everyone fails."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-3",
			"front": "When working as an independent health care group member, the EMT should expect that he or she:\n\nA. does not have to wait for an assignment before performing a task.\nB. will be specifically instructed on how to perform a specific task.\nC. will rely on the group leader for making virtually all decisions.\nD. will receive no support or guidance from an EMS supervisor.\nSee Dependent, Independent, and Interdependent Groups",
			"back": "does not have to wait for an assignment before performing a task."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-4",
			"front": "EMTs and other health care providers function as a true team when they work:\n\nA. interdependently.\nB. dependently.\nC. under standing orders.\nD. independently.\nSee Dependent, Independent, and Interdependent Groups",
			"back": "interdependently."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-5",
			"front": "EMTs arrive at the scene of an ill person. The EMR, who arrived before the EMTs, advises that the patient had a syncopal episode. The patient is conscious and alert and remains so throughout transport. When transferring patient care to the emergency department nurse, the EMT should advise the nurse that:\n\nA. there is no evidence to support the syncopal episode.\nB. the EMR was probably mistaken about the episode.\nC. the patient had a reported syncopal episode.\nD. she should contact the EMR about the incident.\nSee Transfer of Patient Care",
			"back": "the patient had a reported syncopal episode."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-6",
			"front": "While caring for a patient, the EMT states to her partner, “Why even splint the patient’s leg if they’re only going to remove it in the ED?” This statement indicates that:\n\nA. the EMT does not trust the hospital staff.\nB. the EMT’s focus is not on the common goal.\nC. the patient’s leg does not require splinting.\nD. the EMT is being realistic in her thinking.\nSee Effective Team Performance",
			"back": "the EMT’s focus is not on the common goal."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-7",
			"front": "If a problem with a team member is not directly or immediately impacting patient care, the team leader should:\n\nA. discuss the problem after the call.\nB. contact the medical director at once.\nC. ignore the problem to avoid conflict.\nD. engage the team member at once.\nSee Troubleshooting Team Conflicts",
			"back": "discuss the problem after the call."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-8",
			"front": "Premature diagnosis during a call can be due to what error?\n\nA. Streamlining\nB. Anchoring\nC. Overconfidence\nD. Bias\nSee Critical Thinking and Clinical Decision Making in EMS",
			"back": "Anchoring"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-9",
			"front": "An effective team leader should:\n\nA. perform all difficult interventions.\nB. refrain from any direct patient care.\nC. help the team accomplish goals.\nD. command his or her team.\nSee Effective Team Performance",
			"back": "help the team accomplish goals."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-10",
			"front": "When the EMT assists a paramedic with an advanced intervention, he or she should recall that the focus of the intervention is on:\n\nA. completing the procedure.\nB. solving a clinical problem.\nC. following local protocol.\nD. learning to perform the skill.\nSee BLS and ALS Providers Working Together",
			"back": "solving a clinical problem."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-11",
			"front": "For patient handoff, it is important for EMTs and hospital staff to use:\n\nA. common goals.\nB. shared training.\nC. common language.\nD. metric-sized tools.\nSee Transfer of Patient Care",
			"back": "common language."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-12",
			"front": "To be a great EMT, strive for:\n\nA. foundational knowledge.\nB. management work.\nC. the chance to replace an EMR.\nD. retraining.\nSee BLS and ALS Providers Working Together",
			"back": "foundational knowledge."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-13",
			"front": "Health care providers who infrequently work together can function effectively as a team if they work in an environment that supports and promotes:\n\nA. discipline.\nB. collaboration.\nC. competition.\nD. rigid protocols.\nSee Types of Teams",
			"back": "collaboration."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-14",
			"front": "In an independent group, you would have:\n\nA. a common set of tasks.\nB. parallel work.\nC. shared transportation.\nD. your own work area.\nSee Dependent, Independent, and Interdependent Groups",
			"back": "your own work area."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-15",
			"front": "The concept of consistent care across the entire health care team from first patient contact to patient discharge is called:\n\nA. the scope of practice.\nB. the standard of care.\nC. patient care advocacy.\nD. the continuum of care.\nSee An Era of Team Health Care",
			"back": "the continuum of care."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-16",
			"front": "In contrast to a health care group, a health care team:\n\nA. is not assigned specific roles.\nB. works independently.\nC. does not function under protocols.\nD. works interdependently.\nSee Groups Versus Teams",
			"back": "works interdependently."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-17",
			"front": "The effectiveness of pit crew CPR is dependent on:\n\nA. protocols that allow the EMT to function without medical control.\nB. defining clear roles and responsibilities before the call is received.\nC. rapidly assessing the patient before assigning roles and responsibilities.\nD. a team leader who is capable of performing all of the patient care tasks.\nSee Effective Team Performance",
			"back": "defining clear roles and responsibilities before the call is received."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-18",
			"front": "Which comes first in EMS decision making?\n\nA. Data interpretation\nB. Planning\nC. Data gathering\nD. Team communication\nSee Critical Thinking and Clinical Decision Making in EMS",
			"back": "Data gathering"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-19",
			"front": "Which of the following would the EMT MOST likely be asked to do when assisting a paramedic with endotracheal intubation?\n\nA. Suction under direct laryngoscopy\nB. Visualization of the vocal cords\nC. Placement of the endotracheal tube\nD. Preoxygenation with a BVM\nSee BLS and ALS Providers Working Together",
			"back": "Preoxygenation with a BVM"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-20",
			"front": "Which of the following would MOST likely facilitate an accurate and effective verbal handoff report at the hospital?\n\nA. Clearly identifying your EMS certification level.\nB. Brief pause in care to provide the verbal report.\nC. Providing the handoff report only to a physician.\nD. Use of a mutually agreed-upon handoff format.\nSee Transfer of Patient Care",
			"back": "Use of a mutually agreed-upon handoff format."
		}
	],
	"category": {
		"value": "chapter-09",
		"label": "Chapter 9"
	},
	"tags": [
		{
			"value": "multiple-choice",
			"label": "Multiple Choice"
		}
	]
}